Yevhenii Poznii

Python Developer

+38 063 055-29-04

E-mail: epozniy@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/evhenii-poznii/

GitHub: github.com/K1SKEE

Personal summary

Junior Software Developer with 1+ years of experience is seeking to apply and expand my knowledge and skills toward working in a collaborative environment to develop quality software solutions that address and solve business problems, and to grow up as a specialist. Sure, I will be a good employee for your team and will not waste your time.

Experience

05/2022 - present

Podiya, Kyiv - Python Developer

- working as a volunteer;
- implement REST API;
- implement crawler service for crawling FB posts;
- implement integration tests for REST API using local DynamoDB;
- Tech stack: Python, DynamoDB, AWS lambda, serverless.

06/2019 - 09/2020

NDA, Kyiv - Media Buyer

- work with Facebook ad rooms, generate conversions, run ads, and track traffic;
- targeted Facebook advertising;
- buying traffic on FB for product offers;
- optimization and control of advertising campaigns;
- management of advertising budgets.

Pet-projects

Automated Teller Machine:

- Developed a prototype of a real ATM in the console using OOP concepts;
- <u>Developed ATM using Django web framework;</u>
- Developed API for ATM using Django REST Framework;
- Developed frontend for API ATM using ReactJS;
- Implemented register, login, withdraw, deposit, transfer methods, change pin-code, history transaction, open new card in USD, EUR, UAH currency, and exchange currency.

Key skills

Python, Django, Django REST Framework, JavaScript, ReactJS, HTML5, CSS3, Git, OOP, PostgreSQL, DynamoDB, Unittest, Docker, Postman

Education

2018 - 2020

National University of Civil Defense of Ukraine, Kharkiv - master's degree

Program Subject Area "Environmental Protection Technologies". Educational Program "Technogenic and Ecological Safety".

2015 - 2018

National Aviation University, Kyiv - bachelor's degree

Faculty of Finance and Entrepreneurship, majoring in Finance and Credit.